

Nikita Koryakov

DEVOPS ENGINEER

CONTACT



(\$\) +7 (987) 085-90-94



n987085904@yandex.ru



https://t.me/nikita_koryakov

ABOUT ME

I'm 22 years old. I have a bachelor's degree in Informatics and Computer Engineering. Hard-working, creative and proactive. Today, I am a DevOps middle engineer. Ambitious, eager to keep growing and evolving in my profession. Constantly developing new skills and abilities.

COMPETENCES

- Kubernetes(Openshift), Docker
- Java, C++
- Spring core, Spring Boot, Hibernate
- rest api, ajax, jquery, HTML, CSS
- · Postgresql, SQL
- CI/CD Jenkins
- Hashicorp vault

LANGUAGES

Russian - Native English-Intermediate

EDUCATION

School programming 21

Full-time programming school from Sber. It is a franchise of the French "School 42" 2021 - currently

Nizhny Novgorod State Technical University

Specialty - Computer Science and Computer engineering 2018 - 2022

WORK EXPERIENCE

June 2022 - currently

Sber, Moscow, rabota.sber.ru Financial Sector • Banking Middle engineer Jenkins, Kubernetes, Docker, CI/CD, Groovy, SQL, Linux

February 2021 – June 2022

Techstroymarket Nizhny Novgorod, www.tsmnn.ru Retail • Internet Store Junior developer Completion of the components of the online store, configuration and maintenance of the PC. Git • Git • Linux • Nginx • PHP • Ajax • 1С-Битрикс